Okay. Well, let's see what happens if we split them by gender.
让我们看看 如果按性别分类会发生什么
If we split them by gender,
如果我们按性别分类
we see that the women downloaded WhatsApp and Pokemon Go,
我们会发现女性均下载了 WhatsApp 和 Pokemon Go
while the men downloaded Snapchat and Pokemon Go.
而男性都下载了 Snapchat 和 Pokemon Go
This tells us a bit, but not much.
这结果告诉了我们一些信息 但并不是很多
On the other hand, if split by occupation,
另一方面 如果我们按职业分类
we can see that the students all downloaded Pokemon Go,
我们会发现 所有的学生都下载了 Pokemon Go
whereas, the people who work downloaded other apps.
而工作的人都下载了其它的 app
This is a good piece of information since from now on,
这是一条很有用的信息
whenever a student comes in,
从此以后 只要是学生
we'll recommend them Pokemon Go.
我们为他推荐 Pokemon Go 就可以了
Thus, occupation is a better feature
因此在这里 职业这一特征
here for predicting what app will the users download.
能更好地预测用户将下载何种 app
So, we can go ahead and make that decision.
我们就可以据此做出决策
We'll do it by creating a node here that says,
创建一个这样的结点
"To everybody that goes to school,
凡是去学校学习的
we'll recommend Pokemon Go.
我们都将推荐 Pokemon Go
And for the ones that work, let's see."
而对于工作的 先暂时搁置
If we forget about the students,
除去学生
now will look at the people who work.
我们再来看看工作的人
And now, it turns out that the gender split will help us.
现在 我们可以发现按性别分类可以帮到我们
Because the women downloaded WhatsApp,
因为女性下载 WhatsApp
and the men downloaded Snapchat.
男性下载 Snapchat
So, let's do that. Let's add another node here.
因此 我们在这里增加一个结点
The new node says "If you work,
这个结点是 如果你工作
then I'll ask for your gender.
我们会接着确定你的性别
And if the gender is female, we'll recommend WhatsApp.
如果你是女性 我们将推荐 WhatsApp
And if the gender is male,
如果是男性
we'll recommend Snapchat." And we're done.
我们将推荐 Snapchat
So quick summary. If we got a student,
快速总结 如果是学生
well recommend them Pokemon Go.
我们将推荐 Pokemon Go
If we get someone who works, we'll ask for the gender.
如果是工作的人 我们将继续确定性别
If it's a woman, we'll recommend her WhatsApp.
如果是女性 我们将为她推荐 WhatsApp
And if it's a man,
如果是男性
we'll recommend him Snapchat.
我们将为他推荐 Snapchat
Now, what we need to figure out is,
现在 我们需要做的就是弄清楚
how do we get the computer to measure the two features,
如何让电脑测量出这两个特征
and figure out that occupation is a better feature to split by? We will learn that later.
并让它知道首先按职业进行分类 这点我们将在后面进行学习